Once long ago, in the deep blue below.
很久很久之前   在大海深处
Don't be silly, grandmother. Everybody knows there's no such thing as Mermaids.
别闹了   奶奶 谁都知道世上根本没有美人鱼
-You won't say that if you had met one. -You've met a mermaid?
-如果你真的见过她   就不会这么说了 -你见过美人鱼
There is a powerful magic in you, a spirit of the ocean.
你拥有强大的魔法   海洋之魂
Let me introduce you, to your dreams.
让我带大家进入梦幻世界吧
The little mermaid of the Mississippi.
密西西比的小美人鱼
Look, isn't it...
快看   是不是
Beautiful.
很美
Sorry, I have to go.
对不起   我得走了
Elizabeth.
伊丽莎白
How could this be?
这怎么可能
It's Locke.
是Locke
He knows everything to summon me!
他知道怎么召唤我
We have to save her.
我们得救她
She's changing.
她在转化
Her soul is mine.
她的灵魂在我手里
Take it.
收好
Steal me away.
把我带走
I believe.
我相信
Mississippi's always been magic.
密西西比一直是个神奇的地方
Elizabeth, please.
伊丽莎白   活下去